http://www.biordi.com/pages/privacy-policy

Sign up to receive exclusive updates on the latest
collections, special offers, events and more.
Enter your email and receive 10% off your entire order.*
By submitting your email address you agree to receive Biordi
emails and accept the Terms and Conditions of our site.
*Some exclusions apply
do not show this again
Just added to your cart
Qty:
View cart ()
Continue shopping
Our Landmark Store in North Beach San Francisco is open!
Private Appointments Available.
Please allow 1 week shipping delay due to Covid-19 safety precautions
FRUTTA, ROSA
.
GIFTS $500 AND UNDER
GIFTS “PRICELESS”
GIFTS $500 AND UNDER
GIFTS “PRICELESS”
Privacy Policy
Biordi Art Imports Inc. operates the www.biordi.com, which is our website to purchase products and services.
At Biordi, we care deeply about your privacy. We believe in transparency and sharing our privacy policy including how we treat your personal information.  If you have any questions, please contact us at (415) 392 0896 or email customerservice@biordi.com.
The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to share with you the information we may collect from you, how we use the information, and the choices you have regarding this information. This Privacy Policy applies to information we collect about you in our store and through our website. By using either our web site or sharing personal information in our store, you are accepting or consenting to the practices described in this Privacy Policy.  The personal Information that we collect is used for providing and improving the overall customer service.
Information Collection and Use
For a better experience while using our website, we may require you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information, including but not limited to your name, phone number, email address and postal address. The information that we collect will be used to contact or identify you.
Control of Personal Information
If you set up a gift registry or account at Biordi.com, you can access, review and update your profile and settings, which will allow you to modify or update certain information. You may delete your gift registry or account by contacting customerservice@biordi.com.
You may opt out of receiving future emails by Biordi Art Imports, by clicking on the unsubscribe link in our emails.
Use of Personal Information
There are several ways we use the personal information to improve service to you, including, but not limited to, the following:
To send emails and catalogs about products, artisans, special offers and events. If you no longer want to receive the emails, please contact us at customerservice@biordi.com
Process payment, shipping, return, refund, or registry-related transactions when you purchase our products.
Analyze data in the aggregate to improve our products and services.
Perform any other function that we believe, in good faith, is necessary to protect the security or proper functioning of our website.
Log Data
We want to inform you that whenever you visit our website, we collect information that your browser sends to us that is called Log Data. This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser version, pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, and other statistics.
Cookies
Cookies are files with small amount of data that is commonly used an anonymous unique identifier. These are sent to your browser from the website that you visit and are stored on your computer’s hard drive.
Our website uses these "cookies" to collect information and to improve our Service. You have the option to either accept or refuse these cookies, and know when a cookie is being sent to your computer. If you choose to refuse our cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.
Service Providers
We may employ third-party companies and individuals due to the following reasons:
To facilitate our Service;
To provide the Service on our behalf;
To perform Service-related services; or
To assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.
We want to inform our Service users that these third parties have access to your Personal Information. The reason is to perform the tasks assigned to them on our behalf. However, they are obligated not to disclose or use the information for any other purpose.
Security
We value your trust in providing us your Personal Information, thus we are striving to use commercially acceptable means of protecting it. But remember that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and reliable, and we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
Links to Other Sites
Our Service may contain links to other sites. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that site. Note that these external sites are not operated by us. Therefore, we strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of these websites. We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or services.
Children’s Privacy
Our Services do not address anyone under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personal identifiable information from children under 13. In the case we discover that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we immediately delete this from our servers. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with personal information, please contact us so that we will be able to do necessary actions.
California Privacy Rights (for California Residents Only)
Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code requires select businesses to disclose policies relating to the sharing of certain categories of customers’ personal information with third parties. These businesses are required to accept requests for disclosures of these policies from customers but are only required to honor one request per calendar year. Businesses have thirty (30) days to respond to each inquiry to the designated address. Each inquiring customer will receive an explanation of the categories of customer information shared and the names and addresses of any third-party businesses. In limited circumstances, customers' failure to submit requests in the manner specified will not require a response from the business.
If you are a California resident, you may request such information from us by sending a letter to the address listed below. In your letter, please provide your name, address and email address, as well as a request that we provide such information to you, by using the following or similar language, “I request that Biordi Art Imports provide its third-party information sharing disclosures required by section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code.”
Changes to This Privacy Policy
We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, we advise you to review this page periodically for any changes. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. These changes are effective immediately, after they are posted on this page.
Contact Us
If you have any questions or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us at (415) 392-8096 or email us at customerservice@biordi.com.
Use left/right arrows to navigate the slideshow or swipe left/right if using a mobile device
choosing a selection results in a full page refresh
press the space key then arrow keys to make a selection
